export const QuestionData = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'Which of the following are called "Key Industrial animals"?',
        options: ['Producers', 'Tertiary consumers', 'Primary consumers', 'None of these'],
        correct: 3,
        marked: -1,
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Which of the following Himalayan regions is called "Shivalik?',
        options: ['Upper Himalayas', 'Lower Himalayas', 'Outer Himalayas', 'Inner Himalayas'],
        correct: 3,
        marked: -1,
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'Who Invented the 3-D printer?',
        options: [' Nick Holonyak', 'Elias Howe ', ' Chuck Hull', ' Christiaan Huygens'],
        correct: 3,
        marked: -1,
    },

    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'Who was court poet of Samudragupta?',
        options: [' Chand Bardai', 'Bhavabhuti', 'Banabhatta', 'Harishen'],
        correct: 4,
        marked: -1,

    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: ' Who got the first Oscar award in India?',
        options: ['Anil Kapoor', 'AR Rahman', 'Bhanu Athaiya', 'None of these'],
        correct: 3,
        marked: -1,

    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'Who is known as the Father of Indian cinema?',
        options: ['Dhundiraj Govind Phalke', 'Charan Singh', 'Raja Lalith Rai', 'Balram Naidu'],
        correct: 1,
        marked: -1,

    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: 'Which is the highest-grossing Indian film ever?',
        options: ['Bajrangi Bhaijaan', 'PK', 'Dangal', 'None of these'],
        correct: 3,
        marked: -1,

    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'Which actor has won the most national awards in India?',
        options: ['Shah Rukh Khan', ' Amitabh Bachchan', ' Aamir Khan', 'None of these'],
        correct: 1,
        marked: -1,

    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'Which director has directed the most movies in India?',
        options: ['Aditya Chopra', ' Rohit Shetty', 'Rajkumar Hirani', ' None of these'],
        correct: 3,
        marked: -1,

    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'Which was the first Color movie in India?',
        options: ['Kisan Kanya', 'Alam Ara', 'Raja Harishchandra', 'Pathan'],
        correct: 1,
        marked: -1,

    },
]